[doorbell chimes]
-[Davina] Hi. Good to see you.
-[woman] Hi. Come on in.
Right over here.
Mr. Adnan, Miss Davina is here to see you.
-Oh.
-Hi.
-[Davina] How are you?
-Fine, you?
-Good. Nice to see you.
-Take a seat.
Playing chess, huh?
Yeah, I love playing chess with my son.
-[Adnan] Play it almost everyday.
-Wow!
-So many steps ahead. It's great.
-Each kid needs to know how to play chess.
Mm.
How was her showing?
How was Christine's showing?
Um, Christine's showing…
I'm sorry, was she here? Like…
[Adnan] Mm-hm.
-[Davina] I didn't know that.
-[Adnan] Davina, what's going on?
What is happening? Doesn't look good.
-Absolutely.
-I mean, you brought her in…
-Right.
-…and now you guys are not aligned.
What's going on?
[Davina] We're aligned.
I haven't had time to speak with her.
I don't know how it went,
but I'm hopeful that it went well.
I don't know.
Maybe this property's value, the size,
might be a little too big for you.
Might be a little over your league,
this property.
What do you think?
I think I so appreciate you
and the opportunity,
but three months is a short time.
Excuses, excu--
-No, I'm not making excuses.
-Don't do that to me.
You are making excuses. Come on, Davina.
I mean, I'm a developer, and I can't
just sit on properties like that.
Every day, you're costing me a fortune.
[Davina] This is very stressful now.
My stomach is in knots.
I can't afford to lose Adnan as a client.
I have to hustle and make money.
Maybe Christine
isn't in that same position.
So I don't think
Christine understands the stakes.
I can't afford to look bad ever in front
of this client and she compromised me.
This is business.
♪ You know who I am, I am
On that hustle, on that bustle ♪
♪ When you're with me make some noise ♪
♪ I keep vibin', sip of lightning
I love exclusive toys ♪
♪ Come on come on come on
If you're with me make some noise…♪
Hi.
How are you? Oh, don't-- The tree.
-[Mary laughs] How are you?
-Good to see you.
-[Mary] You too. This looks so good.
-How cute is this place?
I love it. Oh my God.
I feel I haven't seen you in--
Caught up with you in a while.
-I know.
-[Chrishell] I've seen you,
-but haven't had a chance to catch up.
-Work.
-Thank you.
-[man] Bonjour, ladies. How are we?
-[Chrishell] Good, and you?
-I'm doing well. May I offer you
-something delicious to eat?
-Yes, please. Um, I'm gonna have
-the burrata salad.
-[waiter] It's absolutely delicious.
-[Chrishell] Can't wait. It sounds good.
-I'll get the same thing.
-You had me at burrata.
-[all laugh]
[both] Cheers.
Cheers. To your… married life.
Welcome to the club.
[Mary] Yeah.
You guys are always so perfect.
-[Chrishell] Oh, he's good.
-You really are.
You guys seem like just the…
happiest, perfect couple.
That's sweet. Thank you.
I knew right away when I met Justin
he was gonna be my husband.
Like, I knew so much so that I text my--
one of my bridesmaids that I found him.
Justin and I just lucked out.
I feel I found my best friend and I'm...
"This is so fun." Couple goals.
They are what I'm striving for
in my own relationship with Romain.
So what else is going on?
What else? Right now,
I'm working on my Coldwater listing.
-Okay.
-[Chrishell] What about you?
With all the stuff you're selling,
you'll be ready
to buy your own home soon.
-I'm so excited.
-[Chrishell] Have you thought about it?
Yeah, we have, um…
-Come to the Valley with me, please.
-[laughs] I think we might.
[both] It's more family-friendly.
Yeah, which kind of…
-What?
-[Mary laughs]
I-- So I have a little confession.
-Are you--?
-I'm not pregnant. No!
-[Chrishell] Oh my God.
-No.
[Chrishell] Wait, what? Okay.
No, but I did make an appointment
to go to a fertility clinic…
-Okay.
-…and to get my stuff checked.
To see how fertile I am
and see if I need to, like,
rush freezing my eggs,
or if I have some time.
-[Mary] So…
-Okay.
But I haven't told Romain about it.
Oh, why? You don't wanna tell him?
I don't know. I just--
I guess I'm nervous.
Oh, don't be nervous.
-Hi.
-Thank you so much.
That looks good, that was a good choice.
That looks amazing. Wow.
-[Chrishell] Thank you.
-[waiter] Merci, bon appétit.
It's like so much pressure,
you know, because he definitely wants to,
and it's already, like,
our age difference.
Like, this would really magnify that.
-[Chrishell] Right.
-And…I just don't want anything to change.
-Yeah.
-Because, obviously, you know,
I was married before,
and then I got pregnant with twins,
but lost them.
Yeah.
It ended up, like,
basically changing our relationship.
When I was with my previous husband,
I got pregnant with twins,
and the first one
didn't take for very long,
and then the second one,
um, I lost around,
I believe it was nine weeks.
It was a very intense
and emotional experience
that I never ever want
to go through again.
I mean, I know I'm doing the right thing
by going to get tested
to see
if this is going to be an issue but…
[sighs] I'm just terrified.
[scoffs] Like, if they come back
and it's not what we wanna hear,
then… I don't wanna lose him.
I don't think he's in love with you
because you can give him a baby.
I know that's part of a relationship.
Justin and I aren't--
Like, he's more patient than me,
but I definitely would have thought
that I would be a mom at this point,
but I love him.
-He's my person, so things change.
-[Mary] Yeah.
So I just think he loves you
and this is all gonna…
-change and adapt, depending…
-[Mary] Play out the way--
…yeah, what the situation is.
But at the end of the day,
there are many ways to…
I wanna say "skin that cat" but don't
wanna skin a cat. What's a better way?
-[both laugh]
-"Skin a cat?"
I hate that saying.
There's better ways to… dress that kitten.
-Trying think of something else.
-I love you.
[Mary] You always know
how to make me laugh.
I'm glad you laugh at my stupidity.
["Just Playin' " playing]
♪ I'm just playin' ♪
♪ Big step now I'm walking
Like I'm on the moon ♪
♪ Big dreams
Yeah, I got 'em… ♪
-Hey, Teddy.
-[dog barking]
-[Davina] Hey.
-[Christine] Hi.
[dog barking]
-Hi, how are you?
-Hey, Teddy. Good, how are you?
-[Davina] Good to see you.
-Come on in, good to see you.
-Hi.
-[Christine] Teddy!
Hi, Teddy.
-He's so excited.
-I know.
-He's very excited.
-How's it going?
-[Christine] Good. How was your day?
-[Davina] Oh, it was good.
-[Christine] You want something to drink?
-[Davina] Uh… yeah.
-[Christine] You want water? Champagne?
-[Davina] Um, I'll have water.
Thank you.
[Christine] Sorry. All I have is…
mugs. I mean, they don't even match.
-[Davina] No worries. I love it. Cheers.
-Cheers.
So… I want to talk to you about Adnan.
Mm-hm.
I had a meeting with Adnan,
and he told me you had a showing.
I didn't even know you had a showing.
So it was like super uncomfortable
and made me look really bad.
I'm sitting there tap dancing around this.
"Yeah, we didn't get a chance to connect."
Which is true, but I didn't even know
you had a showing.
That is fucking, not cool, and I'm sitting
in front of the guy, like, uh…
…speechless, you know.
I mean, that was never my intention to…
go behind your back or anything.
I was in the neighborhood with Christian,
and I knew that if I had him in the car,
I could get him to see the property
right then and there.
-[Davina] Mm.
-And it worked, and I'm glad that we did,
and we've been spending
the past two days
kinda going through our Rolodex of people
that might be right for this house.
I wish you would've told me,
'cause I look like a fool.
You know? I look like a terrible agent.
I can't look like that
in front of this client
and risk losing this guy. I can't.
This is years in the making
with this guy. Years.
I took the window that I had
to show Christian the property.
Yeah, but I can't be in this position
because we didn't talk.
You know what I mean?
That's a simple phone call.
[Christine] Davina came to me for help.
If she doesn't like the way I work,
then fine. Go sell the house on your own.
You know, I'm just--
I'm just doing my job and--
This whole situation doesn't help at all.
Like, this can never happen again.
My client is now pissed at me.
I don't know where I stand.
If I lose the listing,
I'm gonna  lose my mind.
[Christine] I really didn't think
going there would be a big deal.
I'm gonna go. I'll see you at the office.
Okay.
["Don't Say Maybe" playing]
♪ Been hanging round here
Too much lately…♪
♪ You were never born to quit
You gotta stand up ♪
♪ You were made for this… ♪
[groans] When you use the coffee
and there's no more water,
-you gotta fill it up with water.
-Okay, sir.
-I think it was Mary. Is she in trouble?
-[Jason laughs] Yeah.
[Maya] Mary's never in trouble.
-[Heather laughs]
-[Jason] Mary!
-Are you gonna reprimand her?
-What did you do?
[indistinct voices and noise]
[Maya] What are you watching there?
Is it porn?
[Maya laughs] It's like…
What are you watching there?
-It's the dogs.
-Sorry, I'm horny.
-I have a lot of hormones right now.
-Clearly.
-[all laugh]
-Seriously, I'm hornier than usual.
Hey, guys, not to interrupt.
I wanna remind you of my housewarming.
So I'll text you when.
-I'm excited.
-[Davina] We'll be there.
-Heard it's beautiful.
-I'm excited.
-Are you gonna have a date there?
-I'm not playing this game.
Oh!
Brett is always the first person
to give us crap about our relationships.
And especially me.
He picks on me all the time.
But Brett, payback's a bitch.
[Davina] Oh my God. So serious.
Good to know. [laughs]
Hey, Davina?
How is your 75 million dollar listing?
[Davina] Obviously overpriced,
so that's a struggle. And, uh…
he's like, "What have you been doing?
How's it going?"
And so I brought Christine in to help
because, obviously, she has great network
of clients and we're at the final stretch
of this listing agreement.
So I'm trying to show as much activity
as I can,
but there was
a little communication mishap
with Christine and I and my client.
[Maya laughs]
Christine had a showing that…
with Christian, that I wasn't aware of.
But her client knew 'cause I saw him,
I ran into him.
We had a mutual understanding
that I was gonna be helping
facilitate a buyer for this listing.
And I have a very, very short window
with Christian to get him into a place.
So I took it into my own hands,
since we were around the corner,
to show the listing.
Bottom line, I went to his house
to give him an update of how it's going
and then he was, like,
very upset that I didn't even know
there was a showing.
I have two weeks left on this listing.
I'm gonna ask Adnan for an extension.
I hope he agrees, but not if he thinks
I don't know what I'm doing.
It does make you look bad, so that sucks.
Like, I don't know.
I think at this point,
I just think we should just work
as separate co-workers
because I don't want
to step on anyone's toes for my efforts
and I just…
I feel underappreciated so…
["All Eyes On Me" playing]
♪ I just like the attention
Baby you know I got tricks up my sleeve ♪
♪ From another dimension
Do I have your attention? ♪
♪ All eyes on me ♪
♪ Do you, do you, do you ♪
♪ Do you like what you see
See ♪
♪ All eyes on me…♪
[Amanza] Get us, girl.
I'm kinda excited about this.
-Car's so pretty.
-[Heather] Thank you. She needs a wash.
[Amanza] You look good in it.
I have the same furniture
from the same company.
Okay.
I have a desk from them,
a bed from them.
[doorbell]
I've got a bunch of stuff from them…
-[Amanza, Heather] Hi.
-[Jason] Come on in. Both of you!
[Jason] On time?
Always. Her…she's working on it.
-Hi, I'm Heather. Your house's beautiful.
-Kat. Nice to meet you.
-Hi. I'm Amanza.
Jason has Heather and I teamed up together
to work on a new project.
And when he first told me, um,
I thought he was joking.
But he's serious.
[Heather] It's gorgeous.
[Jason] So Kat and her husband
own this property.
They just moved all their furniture out
except for a couple of really nice pieces.
Time is of the essence on this one.
Like, seriously.
They're already in escrow
on another property.
-And they've released 93,000 dollars.
-[Heather] Okay.
So, we have-- It's a 120-day escrow.
-We're already in about 15 days.
-Yeah.
We have a 105 days to sell this
or they lose 93,000 dollars.
-Oh!
-So yeah, this is-- it's not a joke,
and we have a lot of work to do.
And you're very calm.
How are you so calm?
-[Heather] Aren't you stressed right now?
-I'm trying to be Zen right now.
We'll use our concierge service.
So we'll be fronting the cost of this.
-Great.
-Probably we're looking at about a budget
of about 25 to 30 thousand
to do everything.
We've started a new service
called the Concierge Service.
Very fancy.
And what that means is
we front the money to go in
and do any type of home renovations,
like scrubbing and sanding floors,
new wallpaper, home staging.
Anything that's gonna make it look better,
so we could get more money.
Then the seller pays us back after we sell
the property. It's a win-win.
Amanza and I, we're ready.
We will actually get on our hands
and knees and clean up the floor
and do whatever needs to get done
to save as much money as we can.
-We'll get work clothes in our bags.
-We'll get matching overalls.
We'll get like cute--
This is honestly what I deal with
on a daily basis.
-[Heather] It's all about the fashion.
-They're trying to just get
-free outfits out of me.
-[Heather] Show us what you've seen.
So perfect example, look at this cupping.
-[Heather] Yeah, that's lifting.
-[Jason] We need to replace
all the damaged wood,
then re-sand the entire house,
and we need to do all that
before painting.
We need to paint the whole house.
I wanna replace some of the lighting.
Just things to contemporize it a bit.
Amanza, you're better at this than me,
but these are my ideas.
I'm glad that Jason trusts me
with this project
because I haven't sold anything.
So I have to say I'm a little bit nervous
to work with Heather
because we had kind of a rough start,
and I just don't know
if we can communicate well enough
to take on this big project together.
But if we can then awesome,
and I'll prove to everybody what I can do.
[Jason] This house is gonna sell
because of this really big outdoor space.
[Amanza] Heather, watch this.
-[Jason laughs] Jesus Christ.
-So we need to fix the floor. [laughs]
[Jason] We gotta fix the floor.
I think this is such a great backyard.
So beautiful.
-Is that another spa?
-[Kat] It is another spa. It's actually
the best place to see the view.
So we put an additional one.
[Jason] It's when they get in a fight.
They each get their own spot.
That makes sense.
[Jason] I wanna go to the bedrooms
with you guys as well.
What do you think
about the fireplace cover?
[Heather] Leave that? Or…
-It closes the room down. Get rid of it.
-[Amanza] I like it.
I'd say remove it.
-Two against one.
-[Jason] Kat? Remove or keep?
-I think remove it.
-[Jason] Yes, thank you.
-[Jason, Heather] Three against one.
-[Amanza] One designer…
-[Heather laughs] I know.
-…three opinions.
Jason just wants to torture me
for some reason,
pairing me up with Amanza
for this Fennel property.
She's the last person
that I wanna work with right now.
She shows up late
to a listing appointment for my client.
So I'm worried that she's gonna be late
to a lot of appointments
that we have and drop the ball.
So no, I don't think
she's gonna be good to work with.
I don't trust her at this point,
and I'm worried
that it's all gonna go to shit.
-[Jason] Oh! There's a… music studio.
-[Kat] There's a music studio as well.
-[Kat] Wait, where?
-[Amanza] It's kind of a big deal.
Could it be turned into
a movie theater or something?
-Absolutely. Yeah.
-[Jason] That's a good question.
But if we find a music producer or a DJ,
they're gonna value that room at…
A quarter million, they spent on it.
-Wow!
-Or someone with a crying newborn?
-[all laugh]
-[Jason] Yeah. Alright, so next steps,
I'm gonna have you guys coordinate
with wood people, painters.
We'll have to get it staged. Artwork.
Tell her about the artwork.
I actually own an art gallery, Art Angels.
So if you guys want art
as part of the staging,
I can help you out.
-[Jason] We definitely do.
-That's amazing.
-[Jason] It will save us money as well.
-Yeah, absolutely.
We'll get started right away.
Yeah. Let's have a meeting
so we can write everything down and--
We'll figure it out.
-Thank you, Kat.
-Thank you.
♪ I ain't no paint by numbers
It's dark between the lines ♪
♪ Show me the colors
Oh oh oh oh oh… ♪
[Christine] I'm so lazy.
I haven't shaved my legs in, like, a week.
[Amanza] Do you have laser?
No, but it's blonde,
so I don't really care.
I can never shave my knees. Literally.
I'm trying the undercarriage right now.
I like to grow like a bush sometimes,
so I--
-[Amanza] A bush or like a landing strip?
-No, a bush.
I haven't scared Tarek yet,
it's probably gonna come soon.
-Oh my God, I love it.
-I do too. I mix it up.
[Amanza] Christine's probably
got cornrows and bedazzles.
[Christine] It's hanging down
with jewels and shit. [laughs]
Mine's not like a fluffy bush.
Mine grows perfect. I must be honest.
-Like, it's very perfect.
-[Chrishell] Jason is literally gonna--
It looks really sexy, it does.
-[Heather] I like to switch it up.
-Heather.
It's sexy, trust me.
-It's hot. You get like a new vagina.
-[Amanza] I'd love to get a new vagina.
[women laughing]
Oh my God.
[Chrishell] I have a question for you.
I want to throw an event for a charity.
Before I bring it to Jason,
if you guys would be up
for something like that.
[all] A hundred percent. Yeah.
I have this charity I've been working with
a long time that I'd love to give back to.
[Amanza] What's your charity?
[Chrishell] It's called Upward Bound House
and it's for the homeless.
We basically give them all the tools
so that they hopefully
will never be homeless again.
-That's so good.
-[Amanza] That's awesome.
I was just thinking 'cause you had
your wedding at one of your listings
-Yeah.
-It kinda made me start thinking like--
-My God. Do it in one of your listings!
-That's what I mean.
We all have ways of spinning open houses.
Burgers and Botox
is perfect for Christine,
but I'm not really…
stick-needles-in-people's-faces
kind of person.
So I'm thinking, you know,
maybe bring my charity into this
and not only sell
these amazing multi-million-dollar homes,
but be able to give back
to people that don't have housing.
It's basically like doing
a big brokers' event
except that I'm adding a few auction items
and some music.
[Heather] You should auction off
Justin for a date.
-I don't know if that's allowed, but…
-I'll get a signed cast poster,
or something like that or… I'll definitely
get something from the show.
But I'll leave him out of it as far as…
-[Chrishell] Let me talk to Jason. Okay.
-[Davina] Go, Chrishell.
We've put it together. Thanks, guys.
Let me ask you a question.
When you guys
get like random text messages…
-You probably heard us gabbing.
-[Jason] A bit.
I was wondering if you'd be open
to co-sponsoring a charity event with me.
If I do the whole thing,
you don't have to do anything,
but just basically use it
to try and sell Coldwater.
You'll have the charity event
at one of our listings?
I haven't gotten it approved
by the seller yet,
but I think he would be open to it,
'cause it'd basically be
like a broker's open,
but just with some auction items.
And then everybody could come
and kind of shop for a cause.
The answer is…
Yes, I like it.
-Thanks, guys.
-Good luck, it'll be a lot of preparation.
-I got it.
-It's a great idea.
We can donate some auction items.
Let me know what type of items.
-Okay, perfect. Some Oppenheim white wine.
-[Christine snickers]
[Chrishell] Can we donate all of it?
So we never have to drink it again?
-[Davina] Oh!
-[Mary] Yes!
[Chrishell] Thanks, guys.
We gotta get rid of that chardonnay.
Sorry, ladies.
Yeah.
♪ Don't stop, give it all you got
You might think I'm done, but I'm not ♪
♪ Living, loving, let it be
The whole damn world got it's eyes on me ♪
♪ 'Cause I was not born yesterday
What you know about gettin' hot? ♪
♪ And I am here to play
Ready to play… ♪
-'Sup, fellas?
-[Mary] Hey!
What's up, bro?
[Brett] Good. Hey, honey.
-How are you?
-What's up, Brett?
Look at you. You obviously didn't do this.
-Who'd you have?
-I did a decent amount of it. Some of it.
[Heather] Hello? It looks gorgeous.
I've seen it already.
-[Brett] You look gorgeous.
-How are you?
-[Brett] Good.
-Romain eating away.
-[Brett] Yeah. He's killing my spread.
-[Romain] No.
-[Heather] Hi.
-This used to look nice.
[Mary] Who's coming? Everybody?
-[Brett] I think everyone.
-[Mary] Cool.
-[Brett]  Not sure Amanza's feeling well.
-[Mary] No, Amanza's got a fever.
-Oh my gosh.
-[Mary] Like 101.
-Wow, I love it. Hey.
-Hi.
-Wow. What a spread.
-[Christine] Gorgeous! Look at the view!
Hi, babe.
[Brett] Not one person
is using the plates, I love it.
[Heather] You keep this hair on
when you have sex?
Oh God, no. Honestly, I'll get a migraine
if I keep it on for more than four hours.
-[Heather] 'Cause it's so heavy?
-[Christine] No joke. It really hurts.
Listen, I'm really glad
I got you guys to come over
and check out my new spot,
it means a lot.
Even more importantly, there's something
I want to tell every one of you,
and I mean this sincerely
from the bottom of my heart.
If any of you spill on my couch,
I will freaking kill you.
-[all] Cheers.
-[Christine] Cheers, bitches!
Cheers, guys.
-[Maya] Brett, is your date coming?
-[Brett] Maybe.
[Heather] I feel
you're just nonchalant about it.
[Brett] I am, 'cause you get
way too excited about who I'm seeing.
[Heather] Maybe you don't get
excited enough.
-[Brett] Maybe.
-[Heather] Does she have wifey potential?
-[Jason] Oh whoa. Slow down.
-[Brett] Heather!
"Wifey potential."
[Brett] It's an absurd question.
She has sex potential.
-[Jason] Brett…
-Is that sausage? I love a good sausage.
I still haven't told Romain
that I am planning to see
the fertility doctor
and it feels kind of weird.
We don't normally keep secrets
from each other.
But in this situation,
I think I'm doing it to protect him.
-My baby.
-Hey.
-[Mary] How are you?
-Good.
[Brett] It's a nice spot for a mirror,
right?
-Okay.
-Brett, let's get personal for a second.
So let me see a photo of this Katya.
I have her Instagram.
I don't have a photo of her.
She's really pretty.
She has beautiful hair.
-[Christine] Oh my God, she's like me.
-[Heather] Is she intelligent?
Why didn't you like her photo?
That's rude, I'm gonna like it for you.
-Should I comment? Do hearts?
-[Brett] Just like. Don't need to comment.
-Is she really doing it?
-[Heather] Yeah.
Christine, delete it.
[Christine] Okay. I'll leave
the heart emojis though.
Look at Brett. Poor thing. He hates us.
Oh my gosh, babe.
Guys don't respond to pictures like that.
Let's just delete it.
[Heather] Do we need coasters?
[Brett] No, you're fine.
[Brett] I think you think I'm more OCD
than I am which is impressive.
- I know. We're like all terrified.
-[Jason] I know, I feel nervous right now.
[Chrishell] Hello.
-[all] Hey. Hi.
-[Heather] Yay.
Hi, guys.
Oh, it's so pretty!
-Hi.
-[Brett] Come join.
This is amazing.
I didn't see it at night last time.
-[Chrishell] Sorry I'm late!
-Hi!
-I was telling Mary I was playing…
-Oh, shit!
-…a dead--
-[Christine] Oh, shit!
[nervous laughter]
Oh my God.
[Chrishell] Oh God.
Did you just save my life?
-[Mary laughs]
-[Brett] Clearly, you missed my speech.
[Chrishell] Okay. It was good seeing you.
See you later.
[Jason] Bye, Chrishell!
-Bye, guys.
-Bye, you just screwed everything up.
So…
[Brett] So…
-What shit is Maya gonna stir?
-[Maya] No. I'm not gonna stir anything.
I feel like this is the personification
of Maya's brain.
I wanna say though…
I'm gonna say, but it's not for sure.
-I might have a baby girl.
-[squealing]
-[Brett] No way.
-Really?
Exciting!
[Brett] When you say it's not for sure,
-is it 50-50?
-No.
-[all laugh]
-That doesn't help us out very much.
They did an ultrasound,
and they said 85% looks like it's a girl,
-but they have to wait for the blood test.
-[Brett] Or it's a guy with a small penis.
-[Jason] It could be Brett.
-[Maya] That could be too.
-[Christine] Nice!
-They cannot tell.
But to be fair,
they said Brett was 99% chance a girl.
Oh, small penis. [giggles]
Thank you, Heather.
Thanks for explaining it.
Genius.
-I'm gonna get more food. There's food.
-[Chrishell] I'm starving.
I want some more.
-[Brett] Cheese.
-There's shrimp?
Davina, your listing's expiring.
What are you gonna do?
[Davina] Yeah, two weeks left.
You know, I was thinking about it, like,
-it really only has been three months.
-Yeah.
-You know?
-It's not very long.
-That's the thing, you know?
-It's long enough. That house won't sell.
We're walking away from that house.
Jason always forgets
that I also have a broker's license,
which is a higher degree license
than someone who's just an agent.
I could open my own brokerage,
and run my own office.
But I stay at the O-Group
because I love working with a small group,
I love and respect everyone here.
We're like a family.
But I wish Jason would give me
the respect that I deserve.
[Jason] I think you guys did the best
you could under the circumstances.
It's an impressive listing,
but I think at this point,
we've spent enough time on it.
She tried and it's like, how much?
I mean…
Do you agree with me? Just walk away.
Let me ask you.
If Mary would've taken the listing,
would you give her as much as hard time
as you did to Davina?
Honestly, the truth is
I'm tougher on Mary probably than anyone.
-[all] No.
-Yeah, I'm telling you guys.
-[Heather] I don't think so.
-Absolutely no way.
-Oh, come on.
-[Jason] I probably--
I get on Mary more
than I do with you guys.
-Because you give her more listings.
-Yes.
[repeating] Correct.
I give her more 'cause she's producing
more than anybody in the office.
[all] Because you gave her more listings!
So…
[Chrishell] Did you talk to Romain?
I feel like it will actually...
build your bond a little
if you go through the process together.
I could be wrong, but I'm just saying.
That's just my opinion.
-No, you're probably right.
-He's gonna be happy you told him.
[Chrishell] You run the risk
if he finds out later somehow
-of it hurting his feelings.
-Yeah.
He's so laid-back and…
Yeah.
…like, loving, that I feel
there's no downside in just telling him.
Then I have to tonight,
because I'm going tomorrow. So…
-I can help you.
-So I'm running out of time.
I can help you.
I'm out of time possibly with my eggs,
and I'm out of time
before I tell him about that.
Nope, you got plenty of time.
I can feel it.
[Romain] Babe?
[Mary] I was just coming over to you.
But you take too much time,
so I come to you.
-[Romain] What's up, my love?
-I have a little something to tell you.
Yeah?
[laughs] So I was gonna do this
just on my own, to figure out, like,
where I'm at
before I talk to you about it, but…
basically,
I think it's better to tell you now,
so you don't feel offended
that I haven't.
So I go tomorrow
to, um, find out my fertility.
Where I'm at, and find out how quickly
I need to, like, freeze my eggs…
so we have time to do it on our schedule.
If we want to.
Why are you smiling?
I appreciate you came and talked to me.
And I mean,
I'm still happy that you check it
'cause you care about what I want. So…
Alright.
I do want kids. And I come from…
we have a family pretty close.
We're really close together.
So family, for me, it's important.
So I appreciate Mary to make the effort
to see what are the options.
Together. Alright?
[Mary] Alright. I love you. Thank you.
[Maya] The whole thing with Jason.
"Oh, no, I'm not favoring Mary."
-[Christine] Come on, it's so BS.
-Then he's like, "No 75 million dollar."
It's, like, at least I brought my own,
you know?
You think he's jealous
because it's the biggest listing
that the brokerage has ever had?
There is ego involved in my opinion,
it could be.
I see his point.
He doesn't want you to waste time.
But you know what?
Those listings sit on the market
for two years
and then someone come and lowball all,
50 million, and maybe Adnan will say--
[Davina] Okay!
"You know what, Davina?
I was thinking about it.
We're moving overseas,
building other houses…"
[Davina] He has a poker face.
You just wanna know his true emotion.
-Yes, he's kinda scary. I'm not gonna lie.
-[Davina] Yeah, he's scary.
-[Heather] Really?
-Yeah.
[Davina] He's scary 'cause of his accent.
[Maya] We're just talking about you.
-[Davina] Just fucking.
-Talking about Adnan.
I don't know why I'm so annoyed.
I feel like we're spending a lot of energy
on Davina's 75 million dollar listing.
-[Davina] Can we talk for a sec? Cool.
-Go ahead.
[Jason] I don't have much patience for it.
We have not had enough activity
to justify all the conversation.
As long as we're not talking about…
-[Davina scoffs, laughs]
-the 75 million dollar listing,
we can talk about whatever the--
you wanna talk about.
-That is what I want to talk to you about.
-Oh my God.
I've been thinking about our conversation,
and I feel like three months
is not enough time. Not a lot of people--
Can I interrupt? We'll never sell
that listing. We're walking away.
-[Jason] You have spent too much time--
-But nobody knows about it.
No one knows about the listing.
We've spent no marketing dollars.
[Jason] We emailed thousands of people.
We got-- you got an article
in the LA Times, Forbes.com.
How can you say nobody knows about it?
Everybody knows about it.
No, I don't think people know about it
because it's not on the market.
A lot of the brokers
are still finding out about it.
-[Davina] I think we should--
-I disagree.
[Jason] Everyone knows about it,
and nobody wants to see it
because it's so overpriced.
You think you're stealth?
Y'all creep over here super stealth?
-[Jason] And you just line up.
-I appreciate this. I feel your energy.
I think there's zero-point-zero percent
chance of selling this house
and you need to know when to walk away.
You need to know when to stand up
for yourself, respect your own time,
and say, "With all due respect,
find another agent."
I think the most important thing
in business is relationships.
I think relationships are everything.
[Jason] I agree.
-She's damaging our relationship.
--Even if, in the worst-case scenario,
this home doesn't sell,
-she has a really great relationship--
-It's like ten to one.
Shut the fuck up while I'm talking!
[Christine] She has a great relationship
for other potential listings.
So I understand what you're saying
about the listing,
but I think the fact
that Davina has him as a client,
as a friend, as a confidant,
is in and out of itself…
[Heather] In and out of itself?
So can I breathe?
Because I completely agree with you.
That's why she should step away
from this listing.
To protect the relationship
and to respect herself.
You know, working with Davina didn't go
as planned, but I don't agree with Jason.
And Davina's my bitch,
and I'm gonna stand up for her.
I'm not 100 percent sure you're right,
to be honest.
I'm kinda with her a bit.
-[Davina] Thank you. I appreciate that.
-You think more time is a positive?
I just don't think three months
is fair enough to--
We shouldn't have done three days.
What do you think it's worth?
[sighs] So much less than 75 million,
it's not even worth talking about.
So what about
the 44 million dollar listing?
That's well-priced. That will sell.
[Davina] You think 44 million
is well-priced?
[Jason] Let me prove it.
-I have shown that house--
-No, let me ask the agents in our office.
-What do you think?
-[Maya] It's overpriced.
Wait. A little overpriced?
Compared to her listing?
-I'm being nice.
-[Jason] I don't care.
-Do you have any offers?
-No.
[Jason] Here's the difference.
I know I'll sell Hillside.
We don't know.
I have built a reputation
of well-priced listings.
I'm a broker too.
Like, it's my reputation.
-It's the Oppenheim Group listing.
-I know but it's me too, right?
-[Jason] Yes, it is.
-I'm putting my face on there,
-my name's on there.
-And you shouldn't be.
I'm just saying--
When he says,
"I'll list it at 49 million,"
then we can take the listing.
Let me say something as the most
successful, experienced agent here.
Bingo. Jason just have an ego
and he doesn't want anyone else
to have a bigger listing than him.
-I have to defend Jason on this.
-[Maya] Of course, yeah.
-[laughs] Joking.
-[Mary] I have to defend-- Oh, okay.
But he can be a dick sometimes.
Of course, you have to defend him.
I am defending him by me saying
he can be a dick sometimes?
-[Mary] No!
-"Sometimes" is a cop out, you know?
As the broker,
I have to be responsible for your time.
Even if you won't.
I have to be protective
of your time and your energy.
That's my responsibility;
to protect everyone's time.
But it's all about the potential.
It's all about, you know,
what she could do with this client.
Uh, no. We're canceling the listing.
[Jason] That listing's
getting on my nerves.
♪ I don't need their help or favor
I'm certain ♪
♪ Better sit with one eye slightly open… ♪
[Heather] Jason.
[Maya] She left.
♪ These scars across my body… ♪
Was I too hard on her?
Uh, yeah.
♪ I watch them fall ♪
♪ Feelin' dangerous, dangerous
Dangerous ♪
♪ Like it's made for us, made for us
Made for us ♪
♪ We'll never give up
And I'll never back down ♪
♪ Never think twice
Don't bother the crowd ♪
♪ Now I'm feelin' dangerous, dangerous
Dangerous ♪
♪ Now I'm feelin' … ♪